<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Recycler View</string>

    <string name="NewsDetailsAmerica">Throughout 20 years of U.S. military occupation in Afghanistan, the color of daily life dots a landscape of war and conflict.
A U.S.-led coalition launched an invasion of Afghanistan in October of 2001, about a month after the 9/11 attacks, sparking what many would go on to call the "forever war." Over the next two decades, photojournalists from AP and Getty Images, often embedded with U.S. troops, documented the cycles of America’s longest war. Throughout that visual coverage was a pattern: vendors in Afghanistan selling colorful balloons, standing in stark contrast to the dusty landscapes and brutal realities around them. These images – of Afghans holding on in the face of war – offer a glimpse into daily life amid years of occupation.
    </string>

<string name="newsDetailsLandslide">
        Himachal Pradesh: Boulders fall on the road at NH-5 in Kinnaur district on Saturday
An incident of landslide has been reported near Wangtu in Kinnaur district, Himachal Pradesh on Saturday. National Highway 5 has been shut down due to the landslide. The India Meteorological Department (IMD) has sounded an orange alert for heavy to very heavy rainfall at isolated places on Saturday. And has issued a yellow warning for heavy rainfall at a few places in the state from 23-25 July.
        According to weather data in the past 24 hours till 5.30 pm, Palampur was the wettest in the state recording 147 mm of rainfall, followed by 50 mm at Dharamshala, 34 mm at Manali, and 27 mm at Dalhousie.
</string>

    <string name="newsDetailsSports">
        India\'s T20I series defeat to West Indies raised a lot of questions on the Indian team\'s strategy and the captaincy of Hardik Pandya.
        After India\'s 3-2 loss to West indies in the recently-concluded T20I series, former wicketkeeper-batter Parthiv Patel opined that captain Hardik Pandya is "still a work in progress". Brandon King\'s superb unbeaten 85 led West Indies to an eight-wicket win over India in the series-deciding fifth T20I on Sunday. Set a target of 166 to win the final game, in Lauderhill, Florida, West Indies reached their target with two overs to spare with Nicholas Pooran scoring 47 in a partnership of 107 with King. The win was a morale-booster for West Indies cricket after the one-day team failed, last month, to qualify for the World Cup for the first time in their history.

On the other hand, the defeat raised a lot of questions on the Indian team\'s strategy and the captaincy of Hardik, who led the side in the series. Patel opined that Hardik could have used his bowlers better against the Caribbean side.

"Against Nicholas Pooran, he (Hardik Pandya) gave that over to Axar Patel and not bowling Yuzvendra Chahal. Bowling changes and the utilisation of the bowlers are something that tells me that Hardik, the captain for India, is still a work in progress," Patel told Cricbuzz.

Hardik the batter also failed to impress in the series against West Indies. Out of three ODIs and five T20Is, Hardik batted in seven games but managed only one half-century which came in the 50-over format. He looked poorer in the T20Is.
    </string>

    <string name="newsDetailsExhibition">

       Prime Minister Narendra Modi will inaugurate the Akhil Bhartiya Shiksha Samagam 2023 today.
        Prime Minister Narendra Modi on Saturday will inaugurate the Akhil Bhartiya Shiksha Samagam 2023. The ‘Samagam’ coincides with the third anniversary of the National Education Policy, NEP 2020. Ahead of the inauguration, PM Modi visited an exhibition held to mark the three years of the launch of the new NEP.
        PM Modi also interacted with students. During the programme, Modi will release the first instalment of funds under the PM SHRI Scheme.
    </string>

    <string name="newsDetailsItpo">
           Prime Minister Narendra Modi is likely to inaugurate the redeveloped Pragati Maidan Complex on July 26 (Wednesday) morning.
        The complex boasts a magnificent amphitheatre with a seating capacity of 3,000 people. Equivalent to three PVR theatres combined, this grand amphitheatre sets the stage for captivating performances, cultural shows, and entertainment events.
        With a campus area of approximately 123 acres, the Pragati Maidan Complex holds the title of India\'s largest MICE (meetings, incentives, conferences, and exhibitions) destination.
        In terms of the covered space available for events, the redeveloped and modern IECC complex finds its place among the top 10 exhibition and convention complexes in the world, rivaling the colossal names such as the Hannover Exhibition Centre in Germany, the National Exhibition and Convention Center (NECC) in Shanghai.
       The exhibition halls offer seven innovative spaces for showcasing products, innovations, and ideas. These state-of-the-art halls provide an ideal platform for exhibitors and companies to engage with their target audience, fostering business growth and networking opportunities.

</string>



    <string name="newsDetailsIndependenceDay">
          Independence Day 2023: Wishes
1. May the tricolour flag always fly high and instil our hearts with a profound sense of patriotism.

2. We are privileged to possess the freedom to voice our thoughts and have them acknowledged, a right that many courageous souls have fought to attain. Let’s take a moment to think of their sacrifice and reflect on what they had to pay for the freedom we enjoy.

3. Celebrating the freedom that our heroes fought for. Happy Independence Day to you and your family!

4. May our country always shine and prosper. Wishing you a Happy Independence Day!

5. As we celebrate our freedom, let’s also remember our responsibilities towards our country. Happy Independence Day!

6. May the essence of freedom consistently lead us toward progress. Happy Independence Day!

7. Freedom is precious. Let’s value it and work towards a stronger nation. Happy Independence Day!

8. Let’s honour the sacrifices of all the soldiers who sacrificed their lives for our independence! Jai Hind!

9. Sending you heartfelt wishes for a joyful Independence Day brimming with pride, happiness, and togetherness.

10. On this day, let’s remember the past and work for a brighter future. Happy Independence Day!


11. Wishing you a day of celebration and reflection on the significance of our independence. Happy Independence Day!

12. May our freedom continue to inspire us to reach new heights. Happy Independence Day!

13. Freedom is the foundation of progress. Let’s cherish it and work towards a better tomorrow. Happy Independence Day!

14. May the tricolour flag always remind us of the sacrifices made for our freedom. Happy Independence Day!

15. As we raise the flag of our nation, let’s also raise our hopes for a brighter future. Happy Independence Day!

Independence Day: Quotes
16. “So long as you don’t achieve social liberty, whatever freedom is provided by the law is of no avail to you." — BR Ambedkar

17. “May the sun in his course visit no land more free, happier, more lovely, than this our country!” - Sardar Bhagat Singh

18. “It is easy to kill individuals, but you cannot kill the ideas. Great empires crumbled, while the ideas survived.” - Bhagat Singh

19. “We have believed, and we do believe now that freedom is indivisible, that peace is indivisible, that economic prosperity is indivisible.” - Indira Gandhi

20. “Long years ago, we made a tryst with destiny, and now the time comes when we shall redeem our pledge. At the stroke of the midnight hour, when the world sleeps, India will awake to life and freedom." - Jawaharlal Nehru

    </string>



    <string name="newsDetailsBurj">The Burj Khalifa, the world’s highest skyscraper, in Dubai lit up with India’s Tricolour to commemorate India’s 77th Independence Day. The official Instagram handle of Burj Khalifa shared a clip showing the skyscraper lit up in the colours of India’s Tricolour — saffron, white and green.

Messages like “Happy 77th Independence Day To Mother India” and “Long Live India and UAE Friendship” were also projected on the skyscraper along with a portrait of Mahatma Gandhi.
            Burj Khalifa is known for commemorating the special days of countries around the world. It even flashed South Korea’s flag on August 15, which is celebrated as the country’s Liberation Day.
The news doing the rounds that Pakistan’s flag wasn’t displayed on Burj Khalifa on the country’s Independence Day on August 14 is false.
    </string>
</resources>